A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 5, Accession 5 FA1187
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Publications and Reports, 1965-1975; 6
  The Publications and Reports series in RG 5 contains references and materials collected in connection with the preparation of the NCUSCR-sponsored publication, China: A Resource and Curriculum Guide, ed. Arlene Posner, 1973 (and revised 2nd edition, 1976). See also files on the Curriculum Development project, in the Program, Projects, and Proposals series, for information on the background and development of this publication project.
  - Resource and Curriculum Guide: Resources for Teaching about China, circa 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Resource and Curriculum Guide: Weitzman (Essay-Guide), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    David L. Weitzman on Teaching about China in the Classroom.
  - Resource and Curriculum Guide: China Clearninghouse, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    China Clearinghouse newsletter, August 1967 - May-June 1969. File also includes introductory brochure for the National Committee on United States - China Relations, 1966.
  - Resource and Curriculum Guide: Textbooks, 1965-1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Excerpts and evaluations of textbook treatments of China.
  - Resource and Curriculum Guide: Films from the Peoples' Republic of China, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Resource and Curriculum Guide: China Books and Periodicals, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    China Books and Periodicals was a registered U. S. distributor and subscription agency for books and periodicals published in the PRC.
  - Resource and Curriculum Guide: Elementary Level Resources, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Resource lists and ideas for a proposed Intercom issue on Elementary Education about China.
  - Resource and Curriculum Guide: Maps, 1960s - 1970s (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Maps, charts, and catalogues. Includes 12 photographs of printed maps of Communist China showing population, resources, and other features.
  - FA1187:014 - Resource and Curriculum Guide: Maps, 1960s - 1970s; Oversized: Booklet of charts (10.25" x 15") (Box 64, Folder 8)
    Charts concerning Chinese Communists on the Mainland (Eighteenth Series), Special Issue, "The Struggle for Seizure of Power" of the Chinese Communists
  - FA1187:015 - Resource and Curriculum Guide: Maps, 1960s - 1970s; Oversized: Map (approx. 30" x 42"). (Folder Oversized 1)
    Zhonghua Renmin Gongheguo Ditu (Map of the People's Republic of China)
  - Resource and Curriculum Guide: China Books, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Bibliographies and correspondence concerning contributions to the Resource and Curriculum Guide.
  - Resource and Curriculum Guide: Film Lists, 1966-1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Resource and Curriculum Guide: New Audiovisual Materials, 1972 April - 1974 (Box 2, Folder 11-13)
    Materials pertaining to audiovisual materials identified or produced since the publication of the Resource and Curriculum Guide.
  - FA1187:016 - Resource and Curriculum Guide: New Audiovisual Materials, 1972 April - 1974; Oversized: Poster (34.5 x 24). (Folder Oversized 2)
    Poster, The Age of Upheaval Films, Film Inc.
- Programs, Projects and Proposals, 1962, 1965-1976, 1992-2006; 8
  The Programs, Projects, and Proposals series in RG 5 contains the records of four National Committee programs or projects: Curriculum Development, circa 1965-1975; its China Trade Study, 1966-1970; the Ussuri Project, circa 1992-2000; and the Time Warner Internship Program, 1998-2006.
  The review and dissemination of educational and audiovisual resources on China for secondary and higher education was an early National Committee project. In 1968, the Committee produced its Critical Guide to Curriculum Units on China, and later sponsored publication of China: A Resource and Curriculum Guide, ed. Arlene Posner, in 1973 (with a revised edition in 1976). The records in this series relate to the creation of these guides, but particularly document the Committee's role as a clearinghouse for information and resources on China. In addition to the curriculum guides, the National Committee produced its China Conversations series of audiotaped interviews with various China specialists, which it then lent or distributed to schools and educational organizations and media outlets throughout the country.
  The National Committee initiated a study of the issues surrounding trade with China in 1968, and in 1969 commissioned a three-part written report, published in 1970, on China Trade Prospects and U. S. Policy. The China Trade Study records in this series document the preparation and distribution of this report, as well as the corporate briefings held in San Francisco and New York in April 1970 to present and discuss the topic.
  The Ussuri Project was a multiyear cooperative endeavor to establish sustainable land use and development policies for the Ussuri River Watershed, which traverses the borders of Far Eastern Russia and Heilongjiang Province in Northern China. Records dating mainly from 1992-1997 concern project background and planning, meetings, trip reports, agreements, exchange delegations, fundraising, and some follow-up.
  The National Committee administered the Time Warner Internship Program from its start in 1998 through 2006. Designed for advanced undergraduate students in journalism or media studies from Fudan University, the program provided three-month internships at various Time Warner companies for three to six students a year. Records consist mainly of applications and internship reports.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: General, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 14-16)
    Includes Correspondence, Budgets, and YMCA International Program Services (visas).
  - FA1187:001 - Time Warner Internship Program: General, 1998; Still Images: 5 color 4x6 prints, 3 sets of negative strips (27 strips). (Box 63, Folder 15)
    Informal images of 1998 interns.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Orientation Program, 1998 September 15-27 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Original folder title: Mini-SOP Program
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. GU Ming (New York - TIME), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. LU Yingying (Los Angeles - Warner Brothers), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. ZHUO Qun (Atlanta - CNN), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: General, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Includes internship reports, correspondence.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Orientation Program, 1999 September 6-17 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. CHUN Dan (New York - TIME), 1999 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. FANG Qian (Los Angeles - Warner Brothers), 1999 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. GUAN Wenhui (Atlanta - CNN), 1999 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: General, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Includes correspondence, interview notes, YMCA International Program Services.
  - FA1187:002 - Time Warner Internship Program: General, 2000; Still Images: Small plastic album (5 x 7.5) of color 4x6 prints. (Box 63, Folder 26)
    Album of 60 images, showing group of 5 female interns on Orientation and Wrap-Up trips. Date attribution based on the composition of the group.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: General, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 26A)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - Open in 2026.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Orientation Program, 2000 September 6-17 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. FENG Du (Atlanta - CNN), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Violet Feng.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. LING Minhua (New York - TIME), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Anne Ling.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. LU Zheng (New York - Time Inc. Research Center), 2000 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Jessica Lu.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. TANG Yi (New York - Fortune), 2000 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Angela Tang.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. WANG Ying (Los Angeles - Warner Brothers), 2000 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Whitney Wang.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Internship Reports, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Internship Reports (Disk 1), 1998; Floppy disk: 3 1/2 inch. (Box 4, Folder 33)
    One of six disks labeled "Time Warner," 1998 - 2000. Disks were added to this file as corresponding in date, but specific contents are not known.
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Internship Reports (Disk 2), 1998-1999; Floppy disk: 3 1/2 inch. (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Internship Reports (Disk 3), 1999; Floppy disk: 3 1/2 inch. (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Internship Reports (Disk 4), 2000; Floppy disk: 3 1/2 inch. (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Internship Reports (Disk 5), 2000 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    File Plan
    Floppy disk: 3 1/2 inch.
    One of six disks labeled "Time Warner," 1998-2000.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Internship Reports (Disk 6), 2000 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    One of six disks labeled "Time Warner," 1998-2000. Disks were added to this file as corresponding in date, but specific contents are not known.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Intern Updates and Contact Info, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: General, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Correspondence, Interviews, Budget and expenses (1998-2002), International House
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Orientation Program, 2001 September 4-16 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Mr. CHEN Weihao (New York - Fortune), 2001 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    Michael Chen.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. CHENG Yan (New York - TIME), 2001 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    Julia Cheng.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. LU Yong (Atlanta - CNN), 2001 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Lulu.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. SHEN Rujun, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    Michelle Shen.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. YANG Yun (New York - HBO), 2001 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    Chercher Yang.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: YMCA International Program Services and Evaluations, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    IAP-66, Exchange Visitor visa forms, intern evaluations of training programs (for YMCA), 2000-2001.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Wrap-Up, Reports, and Follow-Up, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: General, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    Budget and expenses, International House applications, Social Security and tax form instructions.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Applications and Interviews (Accepted Students), 2002 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    Includes some correspondence.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Applications and Interviews (Accepted Students), 2002 (Box 5, Folder 45A)
    Restricted - confidential material.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Finalists (Not Accepted), 2002 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Finalists (Not Accepted), 2002 (Box 5, Folder 46A)
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. BAI Xue (Los Angeles - Warner Brothers), 2002 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    Vivian Bai.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. SHEN Si (New York - Fortune), 2002, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    Jacqueline Shen.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. WU Dandan (Atlanta - CNN), 2002 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    Joy Wu.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. XIAO Jin (Washington, DC - AOL Government Relations), 2002 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    Annice Xiao.
  - FA1187:003 - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. XIAO Jin (Washington, DC - AOL Government Relations), 2002; Still Image: 8 color 4x6 snapshots. (Box 63, Folder 50)
    Photos from Xiao's internship - host family and visits.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. XUAN Jie (New York - HBO), 2002 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    Janet Xuan.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. ZHOU Li (New York - TIME), 2002 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    Julia Zhou.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Orientation Program, 2002 September 3-15 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    Includes notes and resources.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Wrap-Up (Los Angeles), 2002 December 7-11 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Wrap-Up (Los Angeles), 2002 December 7-11; Digital: CD-R (650 MB) (Box 6, Folder 54)
    Disk labeled "Intern wrap-up 2002."
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: YMCA International Program Applications and Evaluations, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    Mid-term and final evaluations. Application forms for individual interns are filed in their respective files.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Intern Reports, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: General, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    Mainly concerns budgeting and expenses.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: General (Time Warner Interns 2003), Digital: CD-R. (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Orientation Program and Wrap-Up, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    Orientation, September 9-20, and Wrap-Up (Los Angeles), December 13-20, 2003.
  - FA1187:004 - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Orientation Program, 2003 September 9-20; Still Images: 4x6 and 8x10 color prints (6 pieces) (Box 63, Folder 58)
    Color 8x10 print of interns and Kathryn Gonnerman with Senator Max Baucus, 3 other images of group, (including at NCUSCR Gala Dinner?), plus 2 duplicate prints.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Mr. LI Qianyi (New York - Fortune Magazine), 2003 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. SHI Ying (Atlanta - CNN), 2003 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    Tina Shi.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. SHI Ying (Atlanta - CNN), 2003; Digital: CD-R (700 MB) (Box 6, Folder 60)
    Supplementary Material for Time Warner Application, submitted by Tina Shi, June 21, 2003.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. YAN Ji (Los Angeles - Warner Brothers), 2003 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    Jennifer Yan.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. ZHANG Jiexuan (New York - TIME), 2003 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    Anita Zhang.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Interns, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 59A-62A)
    Material separated from folders 59, 60, and 62 (Li Qianyi, Shi Ying, and Zhang Jiexuan).
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. ZHENG Ranran (New York - Warner Music Group), 2003 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    Sabrina Zheng.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: Ms. ZHENG Ranran (New York - Warner Music Group), 2003; Digital: Mini CD (Box 6, Folder 63)
    Sabrina Zheng. Mini disk of Sabrina Z's Folkvalley Radio Program, no. 0101, Sarah McLachlan.
  - AOL Time Warner Internship Program: YMCA International Program and International House, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    Includes applications and YMCA mid-term evaluations.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: General, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    Correspondence and interviews, Budget and Expenses,
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Intern Coordinator Notes, 2001-2004 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Interns, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    Mr. CAI Zhuojun (Chester), New York - Fortune, Ms. CHEN Xin (Gillian), Atlanta - CNN, DAI Weijia (Doreen), New York - HBO, Ms. LEI In Ha / Xanxia (Eva), Los Angeles - Warner Brothers, Ms. SUN Wenyi (Annie), New York - TIME.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Interns, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 67A)
    Mr. CAI Zhuojun, DAI Weijia (Doreen), Ms. LEI In Ha / Xanxia, SUN Wenyi.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Orientation Program and Wrap-Up, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: YWCA International Program, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    Includes evaluations and individual applications for YMCA and International House.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: SEVIS DS-3036 Exchange Program Application, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    NCUSCR application (form DS-3036) to the Department of State for designation as an exchange program sponsor (in relation to the Time Warner Internships). This designation would allow the NCUSCR to certify intern eligibility for J-1 (Exchange visitor) visas (which the YMCA International Program was handling on behalf of the National Committee). SEVIS (Student and Exchange Visitor Information Service) refers to the State Department's online monitoring system for exchange visitors.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: General, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    Namelist, Intern work products, Thank Yous, and Wrap-Up.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Interns, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    Individual applications and documents. CHEN Tao (Julia), Los Angeles - Warner Brothers, CHENG Ran (Ring), New York - HBO, GAO Xiaoyan (Echo), Atlanta - CNN, KONG Dejun (Tony), New York - Fortune, XIONG Min (Isabella), New York - TIME.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Interns, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 72A)
    GAO Xiaoyan, CHEN Tao (Julia), CHENG Ran, XIONG Min, KONG Dejun.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Applicants (Not Accepted), 2005 (Box 8, Folder 73-74)
    Most of the applications were grouped into two sections labeled "Runners-Up" and "No's," but it is not clear whether these labels represent real distinctions between the two groups.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Applicants (Not Accepted), 2005 (Box 8, Folder 73A-74A)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Applicants (Not Accepted) (Xu Jun Steven, DJ recording), 2005; Digital: CD-R (700 MB). (Box 8, Folder 73)
    CD labeled "Xu Jun Steven, DJ recording prepared for Time Warner".
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Applicants (Not Accepted) (Wang Xin, View and Campus Talk), 2005; Digital: CD-R (700 MB). (Box 8, Folder 74)
    CD, WANG Xin (Bonnie), "VIEW, Campus Talk" ("VIEW" is a documentary film; Campus Talk, an internet radio program. Both were created by Wang.)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: General, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    Includes Intern Reports
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Interns, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    Individual applications and documents. BAO Huiyi (Eliza), Atlanta - CNN, HOU Xiaoting (Tina), New York - HBO, WU Zijing (Elen), New York - Fortune.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Interns, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 76A)
    BAO Huiyi (Eliza), Atlanta - CNN, HOU Xiaoting (Tina), New York - HBO, WU Zijing (Elen), New York - Fortune.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Applicants (Not Accepted), 2006 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Applicants (Not Accepted), 2006 (Box 8, Folder 77A)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Orientation Program, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    Includes planning notebook with notes on Orientation and Wrap-Up meetings, and Thank Yous.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Wrap-Up (Los Angeles), 2006 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Wrap-Up (Los Angeles) (Student Interns visit Manual Arts), 2006; DVD-R (4.7 GB). (Box 8, Folder 79)
    DVD, "Student Interns from China visit Manual Arts" (raw footage and "This Week"), 2006.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Wrap-Up (Los Angeles) (Unidentified CD), 2006; CD-R. (Box 8, Folder 79)
    Contents unknown - CD was filed together with the "Student Interns from China Visit Manual Arts" DVD, but it may pertain to the Foreign Policy Colloquia instead.
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Budgeting and Expenses, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Alumni Contacts, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Time Warner Internship Program: Social Security Cards, 1998-2006 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Ussuri Project: General, 1992-1997 (Box 12, Folder 112)
    Includes planning and funding correspondence (Center for Citizen Initiatives, Davis Associates, International Crane Foundation, Wild Bird Society of Japan, United Nations Development Program), Man/Days calculations, 1995, Budget (1993-1995), Contact information (1997). In addition to separated photos, file also includes color photocopies of 6 images from project meetings, 1994-1995.
  - FA1187:007 - Ussuri Project: General, 1994-1995; Still Images: 14 color 3x5 prints in small softcover album (4.5 x 6.75) (Box 63, Folder 112)
    Album of Ussuri Project meetings: Trilateral Fieldwork in Russia, Summer 1994, First Trinational Steering Committee Meeting, Harbin, February 18-24, 1995, Joint Chinese-Russian Delegation to the U. S., July 30 - August 14, 1994, Fieldwork in Khabarovsk, June 1995.
  - FA1187:008 - Ussuri Project: General, 1994-1995; Still Images: 6 color prints (five 4x6" and one 3x5") (Box 63, Folder 112)
    Informal and group photos from Adirondacks meeting, 1994, and Steering Committee meetings in China.
  - FA1187:018 - Ussuri Project: General, Oversized: 2 maps. (Folder Oversized 1)
    "Map of the People's Republic of China" (Cartographic Publishing House, first edition, August 1981) (approx. 21" x 30"); Russian map of Primorsky (1990) (approx. 32" x 35"). Labeled on back "Primorsky - Ussuri".
  - Ussuri Project: Planning Team Correspondence, Study Tour, Follow-Up, and Agreements, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 113)
    Ussuri Watershed Land Use Planning Project Study Tour, January 13-31, 1993. Includes copies of Russian Protocols and Memoranda. Also includes Notes by Peter Riggs (of the Rockefeller Brothers Fund) on his meetings in Heilongjiang, August 3-5, 1993.
  - Ussuri Project: Fieldwork and Team Meeting, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 114)
    Fieldwork, May - June 1993, Team Meeting, September 1993 (Adirondacks).
  - Ussuri Project: Follow-Up Reports and Impressions, 1993 May - June (Box 12, Folder 115)
    Includes report on American Team Visit, May 26 - June 20, 1993. Materials date from April to September 1993.
  - Ussuri Project: Douglas Murray and Gordon Davis Visit to China and Russia, 1994 January (Box 13, Folder 116)
  - Ussuri Project: Cooperation Agreements, 1994 April - May (Box 13, Folder 117)
    Signed copies and drafts of Memorandum of Agreement on cooperation between the Far Eastern Branch of the Russian Academy of Sciences, the Heilongjiang Province Territory Society, and the National Committee, 1994-1996, and Project Summary, Developing a Sustainable Land Use and Allocation Program for the Ussuri River Watershed. Final version of agreement dated April 11, 1994, signed by all parties, May 16-18, 1994. File also includes correspondence and payment letters.
  - Ussuri Project: Fieldwork in Russia and China (including International Crane Foundation Trip), 1994 May - July (Box 13, Folder 118)
    File concerns separate fieldwork trips in May-June 1994 (including the ICF trip) and July 1994.
  - Ussuri Project: Land Use Planning Delegation from the PRC and Russian Far East (General), 1994 July 30 - August 14 (Box 13, Folder 119)
    Brochure, Namelist, Itinerary, Background and Planning
  - Ussuri Project: Land Use Planning Delegation from the PRC and Russian Far East (Correspondence with China and Russia), 1994 July 30 - August 14 (Box 13, Folder 120)
  - Ussuri Project: Land Use Planning Delegation from the PRC and Russian Far East (International Crane Foundation Delegation), 1994 July 30 - August 14 (Box 13, Folder 121)
  - Ussuri Project: Land Use Planning Delegation from the PRC and Russian Far East (Visits), 1994 July 30 - August 14 (Box 13, Folder 122)
    California, Lake Tahoe, New York, Albany, Lake Placid.
  - Ussuri Project: Land Use Planning Delegation from the PRC and Russian Far East (Follow-Up), 1994 July 30 - August 14 (Box 13, Folder 123)
  - Ussuri Project: Adirondack Understandings, 1994 August 11 (Box 13, Folder 124)